https://wallpocketcompany.com/privacy-policy/

Our Privacy Policy - The Wallpocket Company
Skip to content866-662-6200sales@wallpocketcompany.com866-662-6200 | sales@wallpocketcompany.com
Search for:
0
CartNo products in the cart.HomeAbout UsOur ClientsProduct InfoPlexiPocket Sign HolderAlumaPocket Sign HolderWoodPocket Sign HolderFace Only Sign HoldersCustom Sign HolderInstallation/MountingShopPlexiPocketAlumaPocketWoodPocketFace-OnlyGalleryContact UsCartWallPocket Company Privacy PolicyThe WallPocket Company respects your privacy. This privacy statement explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of personal information.We collect the personal information that you provide us, such as when you place an order, request a quote, purchase products online, by telephone, mail or facsimile; or contact us for any reason such as by replying to inquiries by mail, fax, telephone or through our website.This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order or the analysis and support of your use of the WallPocketCompany.com website.The personal information we collect is generally used to process your requests or transactions, provide you with high-quality service, tell you about opportunities we think will be of interest, and understand your needs so that we can serve you better.We do not sell, rent, share or disclose personal information to third parties without your prior consent, except for order fulfillment where we may provide to a third party information that is necessary to fulfill an order you have placed with us. For example, we may provide your address and/or telephone number to the shipping carrier, and if you pay by a credit or debit card, your card number and sales transaction information are passed on to the card processor.We generally keep user data on our server or in our archives for as long as we reasonably need it. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, we may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it.Product InfoPlexiPocket Sign HolderAlumaPocket Sign HolderWooden Sign HolderFace-Only Sign HoldersCustom Sign HoldersContact US WallPocket Company866-662-6200 sales@wallpocketcompany.com
Shipping PolicyReturn PolicyPrivacy PolicyInstallation InstructionsOrdering SamplesBlogsitemap ©Copyright 2016-2017. All Rights Reserved.
| Developed By: Epik Solutions
.HomeAbout UsOur ClientsProduct InfoPlexiPocket Sign HolderAlumaPocket Sign HolderWoodPocket Sign HolderFace Only Sign HoldersCustom Sign HolderInstallation/MountingShopPlexiPocketAlumaPocketWoodPocketFace-OnlyGalleryContact UsCartRequest A Quotesales@wallpocketcompany.com
Request A Quote
Area of Interest*: Acrylic Wall Sign HoldersWooden Wall Sign HoldersBrush Metal Wall Sign HoldersFace Only Sign HoldersCustom Sign HolderUnsure - Would like to discuss Next
Have you ordered from us previously?* YesNoI don't know BackNext
What Industry are you in?* EducationReligiousMilitaryOffice/RetailHealthcareManufacturingHospitalityOther BackNext
X
Login Username or email address *
Password *
Remember me
Log in Lost your password?
